Guide to the Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor 1967-1996 (Bulk 1974-1996) MSS.216
Fales Library and Special Collections
Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor
1967-1996
Fales Library and Special Collections
Taylor, Treva M.
MSS.216
55.5 Linear Feet (37 boxes)
The Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor contains 1671 paperbacks spanning three decades of the twentieth century (1970s-1990s). The two publishers represented in the collection are Harlequin and Silhouette. The majority of the collection falls into the Harlequin Romance series.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Provenance
Acquired by donation from Treva M. Taylor in 2008.
Arrangement
Books have been arranged by publisher, then by numbered series.
Each series is arranged in numerical order.
Missing Title
Series I: Harlequin Romance Novels
Series II: Miscellaneous Harlequin Publications and Other Publishers
Historical Note
The romance novel dominated the popular fiction market in the nineteen-seventies and eighties. Due to its aggressive and creative marketing strategies, Harlequin Enterprises was and continues to be at the forefront of romance publishing. The relatively uniform plotline of the Harlequin romance follows a female heroine on a not-too-tumultuous journey through some exotic setting, the ending of which finds the protagonist safe, comfortable, and in love.
Harlequin's advertising regime took advantage of any and all promotions and gimmicks, invariably aiming their ads at "domestic" women (a notable campaign found Harlequin planting complimentary novels in boxes of detergent). More than anything, the growth of television advertising spurred the success of Harlequin romances. Widespread TV ads promoted not individual Harlequin novels, but the series as a whole; the novels' uniformity was and is one of Harlequin's strongest selling points.
Source:
Modleski, Tania. "The Disappearing Act: A Study of Harlequin Romances." Signs, Vol. 5, No. 3 (Spring, 1980), pp. 435-448.
Biographical Note
Treva Margaret Taylor, nee Hampton, (1929-2006) was an avid reader throughout her life, not only of Harlequin romances, but of other novels and of history. She instilled the love of reading not only in her own children, but also in scores of neighborhood children. She was always ready for a trip to the local public library. Taylor subscribed to the monthly Harlequin service and received a number of titles in each package during the 1970s and early 1980s. Once read, the novels were kept in numerical order by the publisher's number on bookshelves. Her collection is reminiscent of dime novel collections from the Nineteenth Century, presenting a cross-section of popular romance during the growth of the feminist movement.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
Gay and Lesbian Pulp Fiction Collection (MSS.116)
Pulp Science Fiction and Detective Fiction Periodical Collection (MSS.145)
Levy Dime Novel Collection (MSS.028)
Scope and Content Note
The Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor contains 1671 paperbacks spanning three decades of the twentieth century (1970s-1990s). The two publishers represented in the collection are Harlequin and Silhouette. The majority of the collection falls into the Harlequin Romance series. The earliest represented novel from this series is #446, Marjorie Moore's To Please the Doctor. The series reaches all the way to #3410; the collection is nearly complete between 1971 and 1990, with only a few novels absent in that span.
The other series of the collection is made up of miscellaneous ancillary materials included in the collection. Other Harlequin series are represented, such as the Harlequin Presents series, which places the spotlight on particular authors, and the Harlequin's Collection series, which consists of reissues of the most popular novels from the Harlequin Romance series. The small number of novels from Silhouette Books, the second publisher in this collection, is also represented in series II. A few different Silhouette series are present, including Silhouette Romance, Silhouette Desire, and Silhouette Special Edition.
Women |x Novels.; Pulp literature.; Serial publications.; Popular Fiction Series.; Romantic Fiction.; Paperbacks.; Books.; Kirby, Rowan; Kidd, Flora; Ker, Madeleine; Kent, Pamela; Leigh, Roberta; Leclaire, Day; Lane, Roumelia; Lamb, Charlotte; MacLean, Jan; Macgregor, Miriam Florence; Lindsay, Rachel; Lewty, Marjorie; Mather, Anne; Malcolm, Margaret; Macomber, Debbie; MacLeod, Jean S.; Graham, Elizabeth; Gray, Janice; Goldrick, Emma; Gordon, Victoria; Harlequin Enterprises; Harvey, Samantha; Hammond, Rosemary; Hampson, Anne; Hoy, Elizabeth; Hunter, Elizabeth, 1934-; Henaghan, Rosalie; Hilton, Margery; Jameson, Claudia; Keene, Sarah; Ives, Averil; James, Dana, 1944-; Pollock, Rosemary; Peters, Sue; Reid, Henrietta; Pressley, Hilda; Scott, Alexandra; Rome, Margaret; Seale, Sara; Scott, Celia; Silhouette Books; Shore, Edwina; Steele, Jessica; Smith, Doris E., 1919-1994?; Stratton, Rebecca; Stevens, Lynsey; Summers, Essie; Strutt, Sheila; May, Wynne; Mayo, Margaret; McKeone, Dixie; Michaels, Leigh; Moore, Marjorie; Moore, Mary, 1928-; Murray, Annabel; Murrey, Jeneth; Neels, Betty; Nel, Stella Frances; Nickson, Hilda; Norton, Marjorie; Page, Betsy; Pargeter, Margaret; Parv, Valerie; Peake, Lilian; Wells, Angela; Wentworth, Sally; Way, Margaret; Weale, Anne; Van der Zee, Karen; Walker, Kate, 1950 May 7-; Thompson, Marcella; Thorpe, Kay; Winspear, Violet; Lutyens, Mary, 1908-1999; Wibberley, Mary; Wilson, Patricia, 1929-; Westwood, Gwen; Whittal, Yvonne; West, Nicola; Weston, Sophie; Beaty, Betty; Bevan, Gloria; Bianchin, Helen; Blair, Kathryn; Asquith, Nan; Ayre, Jessica; Badger, Rosemary; Barrie, Susan; Armstrong, Juliet; Armstrong, Lindsay; Arthur, Katherine; Ashton, Elizabeth; Allan, Jeanne; Allyne, Kerry; Andersen, Jan; Arbor, Jane; Danbury, Iris; Cummins, Mary; Cranmer, Kathryn; Corrie, Jane; Cork, Dorothy; Clifford, Kay; Clemence, Ruth; Clair, Daphne; Charlton, Ann; Chace, Isobel, 1934-; Carter, Rosemary; Carson, Angela; Campbell, Bethany; Burchell, Mary; Britt, Katrina; Brett, Rosalind; Gilbert, Jacqueline; Gillen, Lucy; Ford, Norrey, 1907-; George, Catherine; Ferrari, Ivy; Field, Sandra; Elver, Rose; Farnes, Eleanor; Doyle, Amanda; Dunbar, Jean; Donnelly, Jane; Douglas, Sheila, 1932-; Dell, Belinda, 1925-; Dingwell, Joyce; Daveson, Mons; Day, Samantha
- Series I: Harlequin Romance Novels
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I contains the bulk of the collection, all within the Harlequin Romance Series. The books are arranged numerically.
  - Harlequin Romance 446. Moore, Marjorie: To Please the Doctor. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 461. Burchell, Mary: For Ever and After. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233257
  - Harlequin Romance 469. Seale, Sara: Maggy. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 483. Hoy, Elizabeth: My Heart Has Wings. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Harlequin Romance 494. Burchell, Mary: Love is My Reason. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 713. Christian, Jill: Harvest of the Heart (original title: Nurse of My Heart). (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Harlequin Romance 737. Beaty, Betty: Maiden Flight. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 748. MacLeod, Jean S.: The Valley of the Palms. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Harlequin Romance 748. MacLeod, Jean S.: The Valley of the Palms (reprint). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 754. Conway, Celine: The Rancher Needs a Wife. (Harlequin Books), 1977; 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Harlequin Romance 790. Beaty, Betty: South to the Sun. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 796. Chandos, Fay: Hibiscus House (original title: Nurse Incognito). (Harlequin Books, 1973; 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Harlequin Romance 812. Neal, Hilary: Factory Nurse. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 856. Brett, Rosalind: Too Young to Marry. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Harlequin Romance 856. Brett, Rosalind: Too Young to Marry. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 859. Creese, Bethea: Irish Rose (original title: Nurse in Ireland). (Harlequin Books), 1977; 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Harlequin Romance 878. Blair, Kathryn: This Kind of Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 884. Winspear, Violet: Cap Flamingo ("introductory copy"). (Harlequin Books), 1964; 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Harlequin Romance 892. Armstrong, Juliet: The House of the Swallows (original title, The Local Doctor). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 897. Haye, Jan: Nurse Hilary's Holiday Task. (Harlequin Books), 1973; 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Harlequin Romance 901. Weale, Anne: Hope for Tomorrow. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 903. Hoy, Elizabeth: So Loved and So Far. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Harlequin Romance 904. Barrie, Susan: Moon at the Full. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 907. Blair, Joan: Homecoming Heart (original title: Two for the Doctor). (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Harlequin Romance 909. Kent, Pamela: Desert Doorway. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 917. Dingwell, Joyce: The Timber Man. (Harlequin Books), 1975; 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Harlequin Romance 918. Seale, Sara: These Delights. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 920. Blair, Kathryn: The Man at Mulera. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Harlequin Romance 925. Hoy, Elizabeth: Homeward the Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 926. Barrie, Susan: Mountain Magic. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Harlequin Romance 928. Burghley, Rose: The Garden of Don Jose. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 935. Chace, Isobel: A House for Sharing. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Harlequin Romance 938. Armstrong, Juliet: The Doctor is Indifferent. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 941. Blair, Kathryn: Mayenga Farm. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Harlequin Romance 943. Kent, Pamela: Enemy Lover. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 944. Blake, Andrea: Whisper of Doubt. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Harlequin Romance 965. Conway, Celine: Came a Stranger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 966. MacLeod, Jean S.: Crane Castle. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Harlequin Romance 973. Seale, Sara: Time of Grace. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 974. Blake, Andrea: Night of the Hurricane. (Harlequin Books), 1973; 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Harlequin Romance 976. Chace, Isobel: Flamingoes on the Lake. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 980. Burchell, Mary: A Song Begins. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Harlequin Romance 984. Ives, Averil: Island in the Dawn. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 988. Blair, Kathryn: The Primrose Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Harlequin Romance 989. Brett, Rosalind: Hotel Mirador. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1004. Beaty, Betty: The Path of the Moonfish. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Harlequin Romance 1005. Kent, Pamela: Gideon Faber's Chance. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1012. Blair, Kathryn: No Other Haven. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Harlequin Romance 1014. Lindsay, Rachel: House of Lorraine. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1016. MacLeod, Jean S.: Two Paths. (Harlequin Books), 1973; 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Harlequin Romance 1024. Wyndham, Esther: The House of Discontent. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1027. Weale, Anne: The Lonely Shore. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Harlequin Romance 1031. Hoy, Elizabeth: Flowering Desert. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1054. Malcolm, Margaret: My Tender Fury. (Harlequin Books), 1975; 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Harlequin Romance 1064. Farnes, Eleanor: Mistress of the House. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1069. Dingwell, Joyce: The Man from the Valley. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Harlequin Romance 1071. Hunter, Elizabeth: Spiced with Cloves. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1076. Starr, Kate: Bells in the Wind. (Harlequin Books), 1973; 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233265
  - Harlequin Romance 1077. Wilde, Hilary: The Golden Valley. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1078. Barrie, Susan: Royal Purple. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Harlequin Romance 1080. Winspear, Violet: The Viking Stranger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1091. Kent, Pamela: Cuckoo in the Night. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Harlequin Romance 1092. Tahourdin, Jill: The Sound of Guitars. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1094. Reid, Henrietta: My Dark Rapparee. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Harlequin Romance 1095. MacLeod, Jean S.: Mist Across the Hills. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1101. Brett, Rosalind: The Girl at White Drift. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Harlequin Romance 1103. Moore, Marjorie: Heart of Gold. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1108. Arbor, Jane: Summer Every Day. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Harlequin Romance 1116. Doyle, Amanda: Play the Tune Softly. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1130. Starr, Kate: Dalton's Daughter. (Harlequin Books), 1973; 1975 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Harlequin Romance 1133. Fenwick, Patricia: Wish on a Star. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1136. Armstrong, Juliet: The Pride You Trampled. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Harlequin Romance 1138. Burchell, Mary: Loving is Giving. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1150. MacLeod, Jean S.: The Bride of Mingalay. (Harlequin Books), 1974; 1975 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Harlequin Romance 1167. Gray, Janice: Dear Barbarian. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1180. Lane, Roumelia: Rose of the Desert. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Harlequin Romance 1183. Lewty, Marjorie: Never Call it Loving. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1187. Burchell, Mary: Sweet Adventure. (Harlequin Books), 1974; 1975 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Harlequin Romance 1189. Barrie, Susan: Accidental Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1191. Kidd, Flora: Love Alters Not. (Harlequin Books), 1974; 1977 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Harlequin Romance 1201. Durham, Anne: The Romantic Doctor Rydon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1211. Danbury, Iris: Bride of Kylsaig. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Harlequin Romance 1223. Asquith, Nan: The Garden of Persephone. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1226. Hoy, Elizabeth: Honeymoon Holiday. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Harlequin Romance 1239. Doyle, Amanda: This Wish I Have. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1245. Burghley, Rose: The Bay of Moonlight. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Harlequin Romance 1268. Hilliard, Nerina: Dark Star ($.15 "Harlequin Sampler"). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1282. Wilde, Hilary: The Shining Star. (Harlequin Books), 1973; 1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Harlequin Romance 1284. Asquith, Nan: Only My Heart to Give. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1292. Reid, Henrietta: Falcon's Keep. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Harlequin Romance 1293. Seale, Sara: I Know My Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1294. Pollock, Rosemary: The Breadth of Heaven. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Harlequin Romance 1316. Malcolm, Margaret: Can This Be Love? (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1318. Winspear, Violet: Palace of the Peacocks. (Harlequin Books), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Harlequin Romance 1319. Brett, Rosalind: Brittle Bondage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1320. Dingwell, Joyce: Spanish Lace. (Harlequin Books), 1973; 1969 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Harlequin Romance 1399. Winspear, Violet: Blue Jasmine. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1401. Dingwell, Joyce: One String for Nurse Bow. (Harlequin Books), 1976; 1970 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Harlequin Romance 1403. Grimstead, Hettie: Whisper to the Stars. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1441. Neels, Betty: Nurse Harriet Goes to Holland (original title: Tempestuous April). (Harlequin Books), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Harlequin Romance 1442. Hampson, Anne: The Autocrat of Melhurst. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1443. Arbor, Jane: The Feathered Shaft. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Harlequin Romance 1444. Garnar, Pauline: Fond Deceiver. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1445. Summers, Essie: The Bay of the Nightingales. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Harlequin Romance 1446. Way, Margaret: The Time of the Jacaranda. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1447. Malcolm, Margaret: The Turning Tide. (Harlequin Books), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Harlequin Romance 1448. Doyle, Amanda: The Year at Yattabilla. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1449. Norway, Kate: Dedication Jones. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Harlequin Romance 1450. Gillen, Lucy: Heir to Glen Ghyll. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1451. Mather, Anne: The Arrogant Duke. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233273
  - Harlequin Romance 1452. Dingwell, Joyce: I and My Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1453. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Benevolent Despot. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Harlequin Romance 1454. Smith, Doris E.: Seven of Magpies. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1455. Burchell, Mary: Girl with a Challenge. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Harlequin Romance 1456. Daveson, Mons: This Too I'll Remember. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1457. Norrell, Marjorie: Nurse Kelsey Abroad. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Harlequin Romance 1457. Norrell, Marjorie: Nurse Kelsey Abroad. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1458. Farnes, Eleanor: The Enchanted Island. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Harlequin Romance 1459. Bevan, Gloria: Beyond the Ranges. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1460. Reid, Henrietta: The Black Delaney. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Harlequin Romance 1461. Danbury, Iris: Island of Mermaids. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1462. Donnelly, Jane: The Man in the Next Room. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Harlequin Romance 1463. Westwood, Gwen: The Emerald Cuckoo. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1464. Airlie, Catherine: The Unlived Year. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Harlequin Romance 1465. Neels, Betty: Damsel in Green. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1466. MacLeod, Jean S.: Return to Spring. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Harlequin Romance 1467. Hampson, Anne: Beyond the Sweet Waters. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1468. Dunbar, Jean: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Harlequin Romance 1469. Pressley, Hilda: To the Highest Bidder. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1470. Way, Margaret: King Country. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Harlequin Romance 1471. Kidd, Flora: When Birds Do Sing. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1472. Winspear, Violet: Beloved Castaway. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Harlequin Romance 1473. Ellis, Louise: Silent Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1474. Burchell, Mary: My Sister Celia. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Harlequin Romance 1475. Dell, Belinda: The Vermilion Gateway. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1476. Asquith, Nan: Believe in Tomorrow. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Harlequin Romance 1477. Chace, Isobel: The Land of the Lotus-Eaters. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1478. Mutch, Karin: Eve's Own Eden. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Harlequin Romance 1479. Lane, Roumelia: The Scented Hills. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1480. Arbor, Jane: The Linden Leaf. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Harlequin Romance 1481. Gillen, Lucy: Nurse Helen. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1482. Cummins, Mary: The Monkey Puzzle. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Harlequin Romance 1483. Donnelly, Jane: Never Turn Back. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1484. Nickson, Hilda: On a May Morning. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Harlequin Romance 1485. Danbury, Iris: Chateau of Pines. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1486. Doyle, Amanda: The Post at Gundooee. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Harlequin Romance 1487. Mather, Anne: Charlotte's Hurricane. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1488. Malcolm, Margaret: The Head of the House. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Harlequin Romance 1489. Lewty, Marjorie: Town Nurse - Country Nurse. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1490. Britt, Katrina: The Fabulous Island. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Harlequin Romance 1491. Hampson, Anne. When the Bough Breaks (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1492. Dingwell, Joyce: The Drummer and the Song. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Harlequin Romance 1493. Armstrong, Juliet: Orange Blossom Island. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1494. Ferrari, Ivy: The Valley of Illusion. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Harlequin Romance 1495. Reid, Henrietta: Rival Sisters. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1496. Wilde, Hilary: The Blue Mountains of Kabuta. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Harlequin Romance 1497. Farnes, Eleanor: The Doctor's Circle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1498. Neels, Betty: Fate is Remarkable. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233281
  - Harlequin Romance 1499. Andersen, Jan: The Silent Moon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1500. Way, Margaret: Blaze of Silk. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Harlequin Romance 1501. Hilton, Margery: The Whispering Grove. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1502. Summers, Essie: Return to Dragonshill. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Harlequin Romance 1503. Kidd, Flora: My Heart Remembers. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1504. Thorpe, Kay: Curtain Call. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Harlequin Romance 1505. Norway, Kate: Paper Halo. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1506. Chace, Isobel: The Flowering Cactus. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Harlequin Romance 1507. Gillen, Lucy: Marriage By Request. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1508. Burchell, Mary: Child of Music. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Harlequin Romance 1509. Pressley, Hilda: A Summer to Remember. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1510. Bevan, Gloria: Make Way for Tomorrow. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Harlequin Romance 1511. Cork, Dorothy: Where Black Swans Fly. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1512. Weale, Anne: That Man Simon (original title: Summer Lightning). (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Harlequin Romance 1513. Norrell, Marjorie: Change of Duty. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1514. Winspear, Violet: The Castle of the Seven Lilacs. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Harlequin Romance 1515. Thian, Valerie: O Kiss Me, Kate. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1516. Malcolm, Margaret: Those Endearing Young Charms. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Harlequin Romance 1517. Dingwell, Joyce: Crown of Flowers. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1518. MacLeod, Jean S.: The Light in the Tower. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Harlequin Romance 1519. Danbury, Iris: Summer Comes to Albarosa. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1520. Hoy, Elizabeth: Into a Golden Land. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 90)